Do you ever feel under any kind of pressure or any kind of prejudice?
I mean, golf's quite often seen as an upper-class white game.
Do you ever feel that at all?
Every time I go to a major country club, I always feel it.
I can always sense it.
People are always staring at you.
What are you doing here? You shouldn't be here.
When I go to Texas or Florida, you always feel it
because they're saying, why are you here?
I'm supposed to be here.
And that's probably because that's where all the slavery was.
So, I don't know.
Do you feel in some ways that you can help change that?
If you became the next Jack Nicklaus type figure or the next Tom Watson,
maybe that would re-educate people.
Since I'm black, it might be even bigger than Jack Nicklaus.
I might be even bigger than him.
I might be sort of like a Michael Jordan in basketball or something like that.
Okay, and again, if you have one ambition, say one tournament to win,
what would it be?
What's the tournament that really captures your imagination?
The Masters.
What's the numbers?
What's the thing?
What's the shows?
What's the agriculture name?
What's the culture name?
What's the campaigns doing?
What's the.
What's the ködrő se vist,
what's the built?
What's the на the last year?
What's the Jahgi'a at the Council?
What's the Liebe city?
How many should be known here?
What's the name and has theなる Kim Okay?
What's the game?
What's the name?
What's the name of the Birmingham News?
What's the name of the joke?